<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Opiskelijalle</title>
    <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/infotaulu/atom-tiedotteet-opiskelijalle" rel="self"/>
    <id>https://flamma.helsinki.fi/infotaulu/atom-tiedotteet-opiskelijalle</id>
    <author>Verkkoviestinta</author>
    <updated>2018-03-07T07:49:11Z</updated>
    <entry>
        <id>HY372947</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY372947"/>
        <title>
            <![CDATA[Application round for flexible study rights (JOO) for studies starting in autumn 2018 opens 1.3.2018 ]]></title>
        <updated>2018-03-01T12:09:05</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[The flexible JOO study right enables graduate and postgraduate students to apply for a study right to another Finnish university, for example to complete a minor module or take individual courses.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY372642</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY372642"/>
        <title>
            <![CDATA[Application round for flexible study rights (JOO) for studies starting in autumn 2018 will open 1.3.2018 ]]></title>
        <updated>2018-02-15T13:31:00</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[The flexible JOO study right enables graduate and postgraduate students to apply for a study right to another Finnish university, for example to complete a minor module or take individual courses.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY372555</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY372555"/>
        <title><![CDATA[Flamma- calendar is out of order]]></title>
        <updated>2018-02-14T12:05:00</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[Flamma- calendar does not currently work due to changes in the Oodi system. The calendar function is being repaired currently and it may take some time.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY372153</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY372153"/>
        <title><![CDATA[Utrecht Network Summer Schools in Graz and Bologna in the Summer of 2018]]></title>
        <updated>2018-02-06T13:36:00</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[University of Helsinki is part of Utrecht Network, a network which brings universities together from across Europe, with a common mission to share best practice and enhance the internationalization pr.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY371684</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY371684"/>
        <title><![CDATA[Apply to become a Tutor!]]></title>
        <updated>2018-01-23T11:03:17</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[Are you an active and responsible student with a strong  capacity for cooperation? Do you want to accumulate experience as a  group leader?]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY371035</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY371035"/>
        <title><![CDATA[Application period for LERU Doctoral Summer School is open!]]></title>
        <updated>2018-01-03T15:45:00</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[University of Helsinki is a member of the League of European Research Universities (LERU), an association of 23 leading research-intensive universities that share the values of high-quality teaching w.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY370808</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY370808"/>
        <title><![CDATA[UH’s Funds: Application time for grants and funding 2018 ]]></title>
        <updated>2017-12-20T13:37:32</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[The application period for the grants and scholarships from the University of Helsinki Funds is January 11, 2018 at 9.00 a.m. – January 31, 2018 at 3:00 p.m.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY368347</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY368347"/>
        <title><![CDATA[Would you like to change the scene for a while?]]></title>
        <updated>2017-10-11T16:07:40</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[Exchange and the flexible study right scheme (JOO-studies)  provide excellent opportunities to make your studies more diverse and to  deepen your expertise.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY367092</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY367092"/>
        <title><![CDATA[New grant available for attending short courses abroad!]]></title>
        <updated>2017-09-06T14:23:00</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[Is a traditional student exchange of several months too long for you to be away but you would still like to study abroad?]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY366510</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY366510"/>
        <title><![CDATA[Transferring to the new degree programmes - instruction page has been published]]></title>
        <updated>2017-08-21T13:26:00</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[The University of Helsinki launched its new degree programmes on 1  August 2017. As a rule, you can continue to study in accordance with  the old degree structure until 31 July 2020.]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>
