<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Opetusasiat</title>
  <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/infotaulu/atom-tiedotteet-opetusasiat"
  rel="self" />
  <id>
  https://flamma.helsinki.fi/infotaulu/atom-tiedotteet-opetusasiat</id>
  <author>Verkkoviestinta</author>
  <updated>2017-10-19T04:49:32Z</updated>
  <entry>
    <id>HY365686</id>
    <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY365686" />
    <title>
<![CDATA[Students will be instructed to use the My Studies Page at the start of the year]]>
    </title>
    <updated>2017-08-28T00:00:00</updated>
    <content>
<![CDATA[Teachers – have you started using the Course Pages and your My Teaching page?  The Course Page helps you communicate with your students, and the My Teaching page features all of your Course Pages as w.]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>HY360935</id>
    <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY360935" />
    <title>
<![CDATA[Want to be a Tutor next autumn? Apply now!]]>
    </title>
    <updated>2017-02-03T00:00:00</updated>
    <content>
<![CDATA[The application period for tutoring in autumn 2017 has begun! You can apply to become a Tutor for degree students or exchange students.]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>HY361129</id>
    <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY361129" />
    <title>
<![CDATA[Kandipalaute – The Finnish Bachelor’s Graduate Survey has been renewed]]>
    </title>
    <updated>2017-01-30T10:07:00</updated>
    <content>
<![CDATA[The national student feedback survey of Finnish universities has been renewed. From the beginning of 2017, the survey is based on the HowULearn questionnaire developed at the University of Helsinki.]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>HY360212</id>
    <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY360212" />
    <title>
<![CDATA[You can now publish student grades on the Course Page ]]>
    </title>
    <updated>2016-12-22T11:25:00</updated>
    <content>
<![CDATA[The Course Page, which can be found through the My Studies and My  Teaching pages, now includes a new feature that allows teachers to  publish assignment and course grades for students to view.]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>HY358948</id>
    <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY358948" />
    <title>
<![CDATA[Welcome to apply for University Pedagogy courses in spring 2017]]>
    </title>
    <updated>2016-11-21T11:40:00</updated>
    <content>
<![CDATA[University Pedagogy 1-2 (5 + 5 cr), also ONLINE in English]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>HY357147</id>
    <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY357147" />
    <title>
<![CDATA[Teacher, start using My Teaching and the course pages!]]>
    </title>
    <updated>2016-09-27T12:09:00</updated>
    <content>
<![CDATA[From the beginning of this year the course pages have been automatically generated for all teaching published in Oodi. Teachers find their own course pages on their personal My Teaching page.]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>HY352849</id>
    <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY352849" />
    <title>
<![CDATA[A new portfolio tool for students]]>
    </title>
    <updated>2016-04-21T09:41:00</updated>
    <content>
<![CDATA[How to present your expertise in a visual and engaging way if you do not have a blog or website?]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>HY352548</id>
    <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY352548" />
    <title>
<![CDATA[Learn more about course pages without logging in]]>
    </title>
    <updated>2016-04-13T15:41:00</updated>
    <content>
<![CDATA[You can now search for courses on the My Studies site without logging in.]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>HY352084</id>
    <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY352084" />
    <title>
<![CDATA[Teacher, are you ready for the freshers to arrive?]]>
    </title>
    <updated>2016-04-01T12:54:00</updated>
    <content>
<![CDATA[At the beginning of the academic year, the new degree students will be introduced to the My Studies -service as a part of the ICT Driving licence course.]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>HY351147</id>
    <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY351147" />
    <title>
<![CDATA[Teacher – come and make a teaching video at the UniTube studio! ]]>
    </title>
    <updated>2016-03-30T00:00:00</updated>
    <content>
<![CDATA[Are you already familiar with the new UniTube studio in the Learning Centre Aleksandria?]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
