<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Flamma-tiedotteet</title>
    <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/infotaulu/atom-bulletin.xml" rel="self"/>
    <id>https://flamma.helsinki.fi/infotaulu/atom-bulletin.xml</id>
    <author>Verkkoviestinta</author>
    <updated>2018-03-19T05:49:12Z</updated>
    <entry>
        <id>HY373311</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY373311"/>
        <title><![CDATA[Iris.AI -artificial intelligence tool available from April 1 2018 onwards ]]></title>
        <updated>2018-03-16T11:52:00</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[The Helsinki University Library has agreed on pilot use of artificial intelligence tool Iris.AI (https://iris.ai/ into). The agreement is valid 1 April to 31 December 2018.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY373289</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY373289"/>
        <title>
            <![CDATA[Training: How to protect your innovation? Patents and IPR for health and life sciences]]></title>
        <updated>2018-03-15T15:45:00</updated>
        <category term="henkilokunta"/>
        <category term="oppilas"/>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[How can you protect your ideas and inventions? What kind of inventions can be patented? What’s the difference between patenting, trademarking, and licensing?]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY373263</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY373263"/>
        <title><![CDATA[Nominate a candidate for the Work community award for 2018!]]></title>
        <updated>2018-03-14T16:06:03</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[The University of Helsinki grants a work community award to a community that has developed or taken concrete measures for the promotion of occupational wellbeing. The award sum is €6,000.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY373259</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY373259"/>
        <title>
            <![CDATA[Effects of the new collective agreement for universities at the University of Helsinki]]></title>
        <updated>2018-03-14T14:22:52</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[A new general collective agreement for universities has been concluded, valid from 1 February 2018 to 31 March 2020.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY373191</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY373191"/>
        <title><![CDATA[Research assessment: The assessment steering group approved the assessment plan]]></title>
        <updated>2018-03-14T12:56:03</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[Research activities at the University of Helsinki will be assessed by autumn 2019. The assessment plan has now been completed, and the steering group approved it at its meeting in late February.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY373237</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY373237"/>
        <title><![CDATA[Joint application to universities begins]]></title>
        <updated>2018-03-14T10:51:00</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[The application period for bachelor’s programmes and the Finnish- and Swedish-language master’s programmes begins on 14 March and ends 28 March 2018.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY360853</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY360853"/>
        <title><![CDATA[Suggest a candidate for the Maikki Friberg equality award 2018!]]></title>
        <updated>2018-03-14T00:00:00</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[The Maikki Friberg Award is granted annually for notable work towards the promotion of equality at the University of Helsinki. All members of the University community may suggest a candidate.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY373051</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY373051"/>
        <title><![CDATA[Lean forum at Korona Information Centre on Friday 23rd of March at 9.30-11.30]]></title>
        <updated>2018-03-14T00:00:00</updated>
        <content><![CDATA[What means Lean-development at Veterinary Teaching Hospital?]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY373236</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY373236"/>
        <title>
            <![CDATA[Fund­ing de­cisions of the HELSUS call for Fel­low­ships, Seed Fund­ing and Vis­it­ors Program have been fi­nal­ized ]]></title>
        <updated>2018-03-13T16:10:00</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[Altogether 11 postdoctoral fellow positions  for two years each, 3 seed funding projects and 4 international visitors  were financed by HELSUS, Helsinki Institute of Sustainability Science.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY373193</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY373193"/>
        <title><![CDATA[Kone Fudan scholarships: call for applications now open]]></title>
        <updated>2018-03-12T13:24:56</updated>
        <content><![CDATA[The application period for the Kone Foundation Scholarship is now open!]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY359415</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY359415"/>
        <title><![CDATA[Please, give your feedback on University Services]]></title>
        <updated>2018-03-12T00:00:00</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[We are collecting user experiences from University of Helsinki staff on the services offered by University Services.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY373095</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY373095"/>
        <title><![CDATA[Settlement reached in collective bargaining - new contract valid until 31 March 2020]]></title>
        <updated>2018-03-08T08:32:00</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[A deal was reached in the collective bargaining for universities on 6 March, as employee representatives JUKO (the Negotiation Organisation for Public Sector Professionals), the Federation of Salaried.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY371782</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY371782"/>
        <title><![CDATA[Minna Canth event for Equality on 19th March]]></title>
        <updated>2018-03-07T00:00:00</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[Minna Canth for Equality -event will be held on 19th March at 13.15-16.00 at the University of Helsinki, Main Building, Runeberg-hall.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY373050</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY373050"/>
        <title>
            <![CDATA[Available for application: Medix Price of the Minerva Foundation and Selma och Maja-Lisa Selander's Fund for researchers of odontology]]></title>
        <updated>2018-03-06T13:53:00</updated>
        <category term="henkilokunta"/>
        <category term="oppilas"/>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[Medix prize is awarded the 31th time, the award sum being 20.000€. The Prize is awarded annually for an excellent Finnish scientific study published as one article during the previous year (now 2017)..]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY367168</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY367168"/>
        <title><![CDATA[Orientation sessions for new staff, spring 2018]]></title>
        <updated>2018-03-01T00:00:00</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[It is recommended to all new staff and grant researchers to  participate for orientation sessions and events which are  organized annually - welcome!]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY372890</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY372890"/>
        <title><![CDATA[Viikki: parking permit instructions now in Flamma]]></title>
        <updated>2018-02-27T14:30:52</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[Instructions on how to apply parking permits in Viikki can now be found in Flamma. The information will be continuously updated.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY372880</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY372880"/>
        <title><![CDATA[University of Helsinki Roadmap for Digitalisation 2018–2020 completed]]></title>
        <updated>2018-02-27T12:08:39</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[The entire roadmap for digitalisation 2018–2020 is available in pdf form on Flamma (in Finnish only, translation coming soon).]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY372874</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY372874"/>
        <title><![CDATA[Info session: Completing your tax return form 17.4.]]></title>
        <updated>2018-02-27T10:19:39</updated>
        <category term="henkilokunta"/>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[Do you know what the tax return form is?  Do you want to hear how you might save a little with tax deductions? Any  other questions about your taxation?]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY372872</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY372872"/>
        <title><![CDATA[Changes to login services]]></title>
        <updated>2018-02-27T09:24:27</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[To fulfill the requirements of the General Data Protection Regulation, the IT Center is changing the login process of some services offered by the university on 6 March 2018.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>HY372850</id>
        <link href="https://flamma.helsinki.fi/en/HY372850"/>
        <title><![CDATA[Participate in the evaluation of academic publication channels (Publication Forum)]]></title>
        <updated>2018-02-26T11:21:00</updated>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[Publication Forum is inviting members of the scientific community to  participate in a re-evaluation of the publication channels, which will  be carried out during this year.]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>
